DAVE SHERLOCK

Web Applications Developer & Interaction Designer

Address: Get in touch:

Blessington, linkedin.com/in/davesherlock

Co. Wicklow. davesherlock.com



ABOUT ME

My objective has always been to work in an environment where technical skills and creative endeavor function harmoniously in delivering a useful product or service to the end user.

I have 12+ years of working with both front-end and back-end programming. Currently based in Wicklow/Dublin, I work as a full stack developer for Sentient Solutions where my role is to lead the ongoing development of Scorebuddy, Flightbuddy and Surveybuddy; three successful cloud based technologies. I am highly motivated, take great pride in the quality of my work and I love to turn innovative ideas into great products.

I am a multi-disciplined developer, with an equal knowledge of both the back-end technologies and user interface/experience methodologies involved in successful software production. I am happiest when developing a web service that is both powerful and simple to use.

Current stack:

PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, HTML5, SCSS, GIT, AWS

Other skills:

Agile Development, UX Strategy, Balsamiq, Adobe PS/AI

HOBBIES

When not working, I like to keep busy. Currently, you're most likely to find me learning about React, Vue.js, Machine Learning, TypeScript and other new technologies.

When not at my computer - I enjoy cycling, skateboarding, beer brewing, listening to music and spending time with my two daughters.

SKILLS AT A GLANCE

PHP MySQL Javascript Vue.js JQuery CSS/SCSS HTML5 Twia GIT/SVN AWS • • • • • • • • • • • Interaction Design User Experience Adobe Photoshop 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 Agile development

EDUCATION

2007 - 2008 • MSc Interactive Media/Interaction Design

First Class Honors & Presidents Letter

University of Limerick

2003 - 2007 • BSc Computer Programming

Second Class Honors

Limerick Institute of Technology

1998 - 2003 • Second Level

Leaving Certificate

St Munchins College, Limerick

CAREER

2009 - Present • Sentient Solutions

Lead Web Applications Developer **Dublin, Ireland | sentient.ie**

SOFTWARE PRODUCTS / PROJECTS:

Scorebuddy

Lead Developer & Interface Designer www.scorebuddyga.com

Flightbuddy

User Experience & Front End Lead www.flightbuddy.eu

Surveybuddy

Lead Developer & Interface Designer

Ryanair

Web Developer

• Bord Gais

Web Applications Developer

2009 • Tricycle Interactive

Web / Front End Developer

Limerick, Ireland

2008 - 2009 • Freelance

Web Developer

Limerick, Ireland

2007 - 2008 • Ardlee Ltd

Software Developer

Limerick, Ireland

REFERENCES AND PORTFOLIO

Available on request.